PERSONAL INFORMATION

Date of birth: 16-9-1980
Nationality: Emirates
Marital status: Married
Address: Abu Dhabi – Alain

CONTACT

Naaaa123456@outlook. com

NADA ALI

OBJECTIVE

I have 7 years of experience in Farming industry and a Bachelors' in Mass Communications (Digital media). I am seeking a challenging opportunity wheremy abilities can be put to maximum use for mutual growth of the organization and myself.

EDUCATION

Bachelor's in Mass Communication-Digital Media Khawarizmi International College, GPA: 3.50, 2019

EXPERIENCE

Silal (2021- present)

Abu Dhabi Agriculture & Food Safety Authority(2019-2020)

Abu Dhabi Farmer Service Center (2015 - 2019)

Receiving Officer (same role at all 3 entities above)

- Organize the inbound and outbound flow of fresh produce at the packhouse/ collection centre
- Inspect and sort products in line with standards, regulations, quality specifications and customer requirements.
- Manage operations at the packhouse/ collection centre by ensuring that proper procedures and safety codes are followed)

COURSES

Alkemy Program:

English level
It skills courses
Employability skills courses
job skills courses

LANGUAGES

Arabic (mother language) English (good)